kazaa.com 2010-01-06

# Music Downloads Now Kazaa.com: music and ringtone downloads.

Brilliant Digital Entertainment Inc. (BDE) is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of this website (the “Site”), our Download Manager software (the “Software”) and our various content download and licensing services, including our subscription services (the “Service”) (we refer to the Site, the Software and the Service collectively as the “Kazaa Features”). As such, we have established and implemented this privacy statement to inform visitors to the Site and users of the Software and/or the Service how we use and protect the information we collect. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy statement.

You may visit the Site and use certain features of the Software without any registration at all, however, we may track your site usage on a non-personally identifiable basis for our own internal use or to share with third parties.

In order to use certain features of the Kazaa Features, you will have to create a user account. When you register and create an account, we require you to provide us your contact information including your name and email address, your age and gender and a password used so you can securely access and modify your details later. 

If you want to purchase a subscription or any files for download through the Software or Service, you may additionally need to provide us with your credit card or other billing information. If you register for our subscription service, any billing and credit card information that you provide will be used to bill you for a recurring subscription fee which may vary depending upon subscription package and billing option that you select. Notwithstanding the manner in which we use such information, we will not provide any such information to any third parties without your express consent except as provided herein or otherwise necessary to allow for change of ownership of Kazaa or its assets and associated transfer of all personal information to the new owner of Kazaa or its assets, in which case your information still remains protected under this Privacy Policy. All credit card related information you provide to us when ordering or downloading files or other products from the Software and Service is maintained by us as highly confidential, and except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not share such credit card related information to any third parties that are not involved in fulfilling your order. 

Our Software is used to make sure that artists and copyright owners receive applicable royalties. This software identifies and counts the songs you have obtained and/or accessed including, if you have purchased a subscription plan, tracks that you may have listened to offline on compatible portable devices. We use this data to report and pay royalties, for internal analysis and we share this data with certain promotional or other business partners or advisors of ours for their own analysis.

We also use the information we collect to tailor your experience through the Kazaa Features by displaying content according to your interests and preferences, providing a faster method for you to submit information to us and receive back the information or products you desire, sending you information about us and promotional material from some of our partners, and allowing us to contact you, if necessary. If at any time you would rather not receive information from us, or would like to opt out of any other service we provide, simply follow the steps in the section entitled "How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?" 

An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are on the Internet. We may retain your IP address and/or other machine-identifying information in order to help us diagnose problems with our servers, to administer the Kazaa Features, to verify that your account is not being used by others, to gather broad anonymous demographic information (such as the number of visitors from a geographic area), to enforce compliance with our End User’s License Agreement or otherwise in order to protect our services, sites, customers, or others. 

We may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Kazaa Features, new products and services available through the Kazaa Features, and special offers we think you’ll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, or would like to opt-out of any other information request or distribution, simply log in using the same email address and password that you used when you created your user account – you’ll then be able to edit your account details or delete your account entirely if you so wish. 

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. Any sensitive/credit information you supply us is transmitted and protected via Secure Socket Layer technology (“SSL”) and HTTPS protocol and then encrypted into our databases to be accessed only as stated above. 

Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor’s hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them. Cookies allow web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor’s individual preferences. For example, by setting a cookie you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time. We do not save any password information in cookies. In addition, advertisements displayed on the Kazaa Features may contain cookies. The companies who serve our advertisements transfer cookies independent of us, and, as such, we do not control the use of such cookies and in many instances have no access to the information collected by them. Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent that or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access many of the features on the Kazaa Features. However, some parts of the Kazaa Features will not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

Subject to your express opt-out approval (see “What information does Kazaa collect and how does Kazaa use it?” above), we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties, including e-commerce partners, who assist us by providing services to users of the Kazaa Features. We may share your personally identifiable information at any time in order to comply with any applicable law or valid legal process. Should you change your mind about the information you’ve provided to us or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal data you gave us. You can do this simply by contacting us in any of the simple ways set forth below in the section entitled “How do you opt out? How do you change the information we have for you?” 

We give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us. To have the information that we have on file for you be removed from our database, or update or modify your details, or request that we not send you any future communications, simply go to www.kazaa.com/login, log in using your email address and password, then modify your details and settings or even delete your account if you so wish. 

Pursuant to the provisions of the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), our policy is to refuse individuals under the age of 13 years of age to submit information to the Site or to install and/or use the Software and the Service. We therefore do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to install the Software or use the Site and/or the Service. If you are under 13 years of age and you have either agreed to our End User’s License Agreement or created an account through the Site by lying about your age, you are in violation of our End User’s License Agreement, the Kazaa Terms and Conditions of Use, and this Privacy Policy. You must immediately discontinue any use of this Site, uninstall the Software and discontinue any use of the Service. 

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites to link to, and frame within, the Kazaa Features. We also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our site) is not received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Kazaa Features and the links placed upon each of them and therefore request any feedback on not only the Kazaa Features, but for sites each links to as well (including if a specific link does not work). 

From time-to-time, we request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Kazaa Features. 

By visiting the Site or downloading the Software or using the Service, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy statement. We may change our privacy policy from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Site. If we make any significant changes to the manner in which treat your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by email or place a prominent notice on the Site. Continued access or use of the Kazaa Features shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this privacy statement. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with the Kazaa Features, please do not hesitate to contact: 

Customer Service, BDE Attention Kazaa  
P.O.Box 862  
Bondi Junction  
NSW 1355  
Australia  
Or via our Contact Us form at our [Customer Support site](http://www.kazaa.com/support/askkazaa.aspx)

Terms and Conditions Please also see our Terms and Conditions of Use establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site and other Kazaa services and applications.
